翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Our next topic-- and this one is going to be a bit of a doozy--
下一个话题很有意思
is going to be the definition and instantiation of classes.
类的定义和实例化
So we've already done this, but we're going to do a more sophisticated version of what we've seen before.
我们以前做过了这点，但现在要做一个更复杂的版本
So let's suppose we create a new class called dog.
新建一个名为 Dog 的类
What I'm going to do that's different than before is I'm going to take away the main method.
与之前不同的是，去掉 main 方法
We'll see why.
拭目以待
Instead, I'm going to give it a method, make noise.
给它一个方法 makeNoise
And what that's going to do is bark.
然后打印 Bark
So we can compile this class just like before.
像以前一样编译这个类
And it'll compile just fine.
编译好了
There's dog dot class.
有一个 Dog.class
But if I do dog, draw a dog, I get this error we saw in Lecture 1.
但是如果我操作狗、画狗，就会得到第一课中的错误
There's no main method.
缺少 main 方法
Dogs don't know how to run.
Dog 无法运行
Now this file right here, I guess, just for comparison, for those of you who know Python,
我们与 Python 比较
this file is the equivalent more or less of deaf make noise print work speak dog dot py.
这个文件相当于...
You'll notice that this Python program, there is no point where it's calling make noise
这个 Python 程序没有调用 makeNoise
because there's no main.
因为没有 main
So the stuff that goes down here, this is basically main, like stuff that lives outside of a function in Python is main.
下面这里其实就是 main，Python 中函数之外的东西就是 main
So we decided to put back main.
我们写出 main
Then we could make noise.
然后就可以调用了
Now if we recompile dog and run dog, we get bark.
现在重新编译运行 Dog，就会得到 Bark
Just like down here, it would just do make noise.
就像在这里调用 makeNoise
That's the Python version of this.
这是 Python 的版本
So it's often the case though that classes we created in Java do not have main methods.
通常 Java 创建的类没有 main 方法
I'm just going to take this away entirely.
把这些删掉
Often we'll have, and we'll see why in project zero,
在项目0中会看到原因
so just trust me for now.
现在就先相信我
Often we won't actually have a main method in the dog class.
通常在 Dog 类中实际上不会有 main 方法
Instead, we'll often have other classes that use the dog class.
而是创建使用 Dog 类的其他类
So I'm going to create dog launcher.
比如创建一个 DogLauncher
So every dog ought to be launched.
每个 Dog 都要被注册
This is a class that, if you're looking at our optional textbook, the dog launcher class will test drive the dog class.
如果你看了选修课本，DogLauncher 类会驱动 Dog 类
So it's just there to show that dogs work.
它只是证明 Dog 正常工作
So in this case, dog launcher does have the main method.
这种情况中，DogLauncher 有 main 方法
And what I'm going to do is--
我要做的是...
my goal is I want to call the make noise method of our dog class over here.
在这里调用 Dog 类的 makeNoise 方法
So what I'm going to do here is I'm going to say, dog dot make noise.
所以要在这里写 Dog.makeNoise()
So what this does is it says, Java, I want you to go to the dog class, find the make noise method, and run it.
这是在告诉编译器进入 Dog 类，找到 makeNoise 方法然后运行它
By the way, I don't think I mentioned this before in these videos, but method is just a word people use in Java for a function.
顺便说一句，之前可能没有提过，方法只是在 Java 中用来表示函数的一个词
So if we do Java dog launcher now, I get a bark.
那么执行 java DogLauncher，得到 Bark
So what does dog launcher do?
DogLauncher 是做什么的呢？
Well, when it starts running it goes to the dog class,
运行时它会进入 Dog 类中
says make noise, and this happens.
调用 makeNoise，然后打印
And that's the core of what defining classes is all about.
这就是定义类的核心内容
So as we saw last time, every method in Java,
就像我们上次看到的，Java 中的每个方法
any code you want to run, it must be associated with some class.
要运行的任何代码，都必须与某个类相关联
Every file contains a class.
每个文件都包含一个类
And all code has to go inside of a class.
而且所有代码都必须放在类中
There's no way to write code that is not inside of a class.
不能编写不在类内部的代码
And so what we want to do is if we want to actually run a class,
另外要想运行一个类
then we have to define a main method.
就必须定义一个 main 方法
If we actually want to run something, we have to have a main.
运行就需要 main
So the dog class, as we saw, as we've written it on my side just now, it has no main method.
就像我们刚才写的 Dog 类，它没有 main 方法
You cannot run it directly. There is no main method.
你不能直接运行它
And that's common pattern.
这是常见的形式
But we could have other classes that have a main method that maybe call methods in our other classes.
但我们可以有一个包含 main 方法的其他类，用它来调用类中的方法
So this dog launcher class, it calls a method from another class, which is a nice feature,
所以用 DogLauncher 类调用另一个类，这是一个很好的特性
that one class can use another.
一个类可以使用另一个类
Because that's the entire basis upon which we're able to break down problems into smaller pieces.
这是我们得以拆分化简问题的基础
And so again, our optional textbook Head First Java it calls this a test drive class.
再说一次，我们的选修课本 Head First Java 称之为测试驱动类
Now of course, not all dogs are equal.
当然并不是所有狗都是一样的
Here is one.
这是一种狗
And here's a different dog.
这是另一种狗
So not all dogs are equal.
所以并不是所有狗都是一样的
And we're going to capture that in our Java code.
我们将在 Java 代码中体现这一点
We want our dog class to be able to-- often we write programs that recapitulate features of the real world around us.
我们希望 Dog 类能够...通常我们编写的程序能够概括周围真实世界的特征
So we want to, if we're adding dog simulators,
所以我们要增加狗的模拟器
we don't want them all to bark the same.
我们不想让它们的叫声都一样
So how can we achieve this?
怎么做呢？
Well, One approach would be for every single dog out there, just make a new class.
一种方法是每种狗都创建一个类
For Mia the malamute, this dog here,
对于阿拉斯加犬，它的类在这
it will have an Arooo sound.
会发出 aroooo 的叫声
For Yapster the dog--
对于 Yapster 这种狗来说
I don't know what that dog's name was--
我不知道那只狗是什么品种
maybe it has this just hideous barking noise here.
也许它有这种可怕的叫声
We could do this maybe, but this is going to get redundant in a hurry.
我们可以这么做，但是有些多余
It's obviously going to be just annoying.
很明显不是好的做法
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）